前情提要
Previously on Teen Wolf...
基拉 你忘了你为你喜欢的小伙做的研究了
Kira, you forgot all the research you did for that boy you like.
没有它我们不会离开
We're not leaving without it.
他们根本不想让我们拿到它
Somebody really doesn't want our hands in there.
我们需要更多帮助
We're gonna need a lot more help.
莉迪亚是有天赋的人
Lydia's got sort of a talent.
我是灵媒
I'm psychic.
你打开那扇门
You opened a door.
它会像灯塔一样吸引他们
It will draw them here, like a beacon.
带他回来 让他闭嘴
Bring him around back.And keep it quiet.
除了必须要知道的人 别让别人知道
No one needs to know except for the people who absolutely need to know.
该死 又来
Oh, here we go.
别想让他进来
Hey. He is not coming in.
-只有这家医院要收治他 -那郡里呢
- This is the only hospital that will take him. - What about County?
你想象不到这家伙有多需要手术
You'd be surprised how fast things fill up when a guy like this needs surgery.
-他们把他扔给我们了吗 -是的
- They turfed him to us? - Yeah.
-郡里不愿意给他做手术 -必须有人要做
- If County doesn't want to operate on him... - Then someone has to.
有人得去做术前询问
Somebody needs to do his pre-op interview.
一般是谁来做
Who usually does that?
我
Me.
快滚下来 有活做
Get your ass down here now. We have a job to do.
哥们我已经上床了 哥们儿你多大了
Dude, I'm already in bed. And aren't we getting a little old for this?
我们是在帮教练啊
We do this for Coach.
你是说要整他吧
I thought we did this to Coach.
不管咋样 你知道的 他需要这样
Whatever, okay? You know he needs this.
他是为这些东西而生的 他会喜欢的
He lives for this stuff. He loves it.
但是现在是大半夜啊
But it's the middle of the night.
应该是12点15
12:15 actually.
意味着已经过了半夜了 现在已经正式成为恶作剧之日/夜
Which means it's after midnight and officially Mischief Night/Day,
并且 十分巧合的是
and, by perfectly awesome coincidence,
今天正好是教练的生日
it's also happens to be Coach's birthday.
如果你五秒钟不出现 我会掐死你的
So if you are not down here in five seconds, I will destroy you.
明白了吗 5 4 3 2
Okay? And I mean five,four, three, two...
- 1 - 我恨你
- One. - I hate you.
要牢记这个家伙都干了些什么
Try to keep in mind exactly what this guy's capable of.
他之前是一个电力工程师 后来带着一个榴霰弹上了一辆校车
He's a former electrical engineer who decided to walk onto a school bus
炸死四名学生 另外一个学生没了腿
with a shrapnel bomb. He left four students dead and a fifth with no legs.
好奇一下 神经科的医生就没有干过什么有用的事吗
Just out of curiosity, have any of his psychiatrists made any progress?
他们说 这样的事 已经屡见不鲜了
I'm told this is the same thing almost every day.
他要是出去 还会再这么做的
When he gets out, he's going to do it again.
下一次 他会做的更狠
And next time, he's going to get it right.
巴罗先生
Mr. Barrow,
你知道吗 伤疤已经把
do you understand that scar tissue has formed around a piece of shrapnel
上次进入你身体里的弹片包起来了
that remains in your body from a previous injury
而现在 弹片已经在影响你的生理机能了
and that it is now blocking vital functions?
明白
Yes.
你是否明白我们必须明天早上
Do you understand that we must put you under general anesthesia
给你做手术 取出弹片
tomorrow morning in order to remove the obstruction?
孩子们还在万圣节前夜恶作剧吗
Do the kids still pull pranks the day before Halloween?
你是说恶作剧之夜
You mean Mischief Night?
在我们那边 我们叫他 地狱之夜
Where I'm from, we called it Hell Night.
还有 当然 我明白
And, yes, I understand.
- 你对什么药过敏吗  - 没
- Do you have any allergies to any medications? - No.
除了助眠药物和抗狂躁药物以外
Are you taking any medications other than the ones listed here?
你有用别的药物吗
Temazepam. Divalproex.
我只吃了你们给的药
I just take what they give me.
我需要听听他的心跳
I'm going to need to listen to his heart.
吸气
In...
呼气
And out.
吸气
In.
为什么你不把你最想问的问题问了呢
Why don't you just ask the question you really want to ask?
为什么你这么做
Why did you do it?
我看见了他们的眼睛
I saw their eyes.
他们的眼睛在发光
Their eyes were glowing.
我看见他们
I saw them.
我看见他们的眼神
I saw their eyes!
他们的眼睛在发光
Their eyes were glowing!
少狼吧字幕组
制作
翻译
小黑屋 小龙 暖的咖啡
校对
harryblack007
压制
小龙
你回学校了
You're back in school?
不 只是找你谈谈
No, just to talk.
哟 这不像你们的行事风格啊
Oh. That's kind of a change of pace for you guys.
你们不是最爱掰胳膊 折腿 杀戮的吗
Usually, you're just hurting, maiming, and killing.
你需要一个狼群 我们需要一只头狼
You need a pack. We need an Alpha.
你在搞笑么 当然不行
Yeah. Absolutely not. That's hilarious though.
你来找我们帮忙 我们帮了
You came to us for help. We helped.
你们把他的脸打成了肉酱
You beat his face into a bloody pulp.
这不是帮助 在我看来 你们是在害他
That's not helping. In my opinion, that's actually counter-productive.
为啥我要同意
Why would I say yes?
我们的力量增强了 我们的加入会让你更有实力
We'd add strength. We'd make you more powerful.
没有理由拒绝
There's no reason to say no.
怎么没有 你们抓着德里克的爪子
I can think of one. Like the two of you holding Derek's claws
然后卡莉抓着博伊德插死了她
while Kali impaled Boyd.
事实上 我现在就想插死他们
In fact, I don't know why we're not impaling them right now.
你想试试
You want to try?
抱歉 他们不相信你
Sorry, but they don't trust you.
我也一样
And neither do I.
现在咋办
What now?
不 想都别想
No. No way.
- 我们还没毕业呢 -我们不需要
- We never finished. - And we don't have to.
如果我想呢?
What if I want to?
你...你真的想回到高中吗?
You... You seriously want to go back to high school?
是莉迪亚的原因吗?
Is this about Lydia?
是想让斯科特改变主意
This is about getting Scott to change his mind.
我们连二等狼都不是了 我们只是低等狼
We're not just Betas anymore. We're Omegas.
还记得那些贱人吗?
The bitches, remember?
当被我们欺负的人发现我们已经没有狼群了
When everyone we've screwed over finds out we don't have a pack anymore,
你觉得会怎什么样?
what do you think's going to happen?
我们死定了
We're dead on our own.
这总比回到高中好
That's still better than being back in high school.
我不会的 没门
I'm not doing it. No way.
什么?
What?
我不上数学课
I'm not taking math.
我替你上
I'll take it for you.
看着点 别砸脸!
All right, that's my face!
嘿 基友 好决定
Hey, dude, good decision, buddy.
老大明智的决定
Good Alpha decision.
希望吧
I hope so.
不 你知道的
No, you know so.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
- 我  - 是你啊
- Me? - You.
你在看她?
You looking at her?
她
Her?
哪个她
Who her?
那个她 基拉 你喜欢她吗?
Her her. Kira. You like her?
不 我...
No. I mean...
嗯 嗯 她不错啦 新来的
Yeah, yeah, she's okay. She's new.
那就约她出去啊
So, ask her out.
现在?
Now?
对啊 现在
Yes, now.
- 现在? - 现在
- Right now? - Right now.
斯科特 你还没懂我的意思
Scott, I don't think you get it yet.
你是阿尔法 你是食物链顶端的人
You're an Alpha. You're the apex predator.
每个人都喜欢你 你就像人人都喜欢的女神一样
Everyone wants you. You're like the hot girl that every guy wants.
女神
The hot girl?
你就是最正的女神
You are the hottest girl.
什么
What?
我是女神
I'm the hot girl.
是的 你是
Yes, you are.
整我啊
Peek-a-boo!
你们就这点儿能耐
That's all you got?
不够看
That's it?
你妈逼
Son of a bitch!
恶作剧之夜 恶魔之夜
Mischief Night, Devil's Night.
我不管你怎么叫它
I don't care what you call it.
你们小崽子都是恶魔
You little punks are evil.
你觉得每次万圣节我家被砸鸡蛋很搞笑吗?
You think it's funny every Halloween my house gets egged?
一个男人的房子就应该像他的城堡一样
A man's house is supposed to be his castle.
我的特么像个煎蛋饼一样
Mine's a frickin' omelet.
哦 还有 你们又要来一遍
Oh, this? We're gonna do this again?
我才不会上当
I don't think so.
生日快乐
"Happy Birthday."
"爱你 格林伯格"
"Love, Greenberg."
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
有苍蝇
There's a fly.
有人觉得我应该划个小口
Anybody else here think I should make a minor slip
让这家伙在手术台出血死掉吗?
and let this bastard bleed out on the table?
这只是一个手术玩笑而已 梅丽莎 放轻松
That's just a little surgical humor, Melissa. Relax.
给我 手术钳
Clamp, please.
吸盘
Suction
让我们看看里面有什么
Let's see what we have here.
哦!
Oh!
好吧 这...这...这肯定不是弹片
Okay, that's... That's... That's not shrapnel.
额 10号刀 10号刀
Uh, 10 blade. 10 blade.
10号刀 好吗
10 blade, please.
你怎么了 你把10号刀弄掉了
What's the problem? You're missing your 10 blade?
医生...医生 你来看看这个
Doctor... Doctor, I think you should see this.
我真的觉得你该来看看这个
I really think you should see this.
走开！走开！
Move! Move!
他跑了 巴罗跑了
He's gone. Barrow's gone.
他没事的 别死啊
He's going to be okay. Stay with me.
嗷! 你还有麻醉剂吗?
Ow! Don't you have any anesthetic?
没有
Yep.
好吧 你至少要告诉我在冒什么险掏什么吧
Well, are you at least going to tell me what I risked life and digit for?
你等下看就知道了
I'm going to show you.
火灾后 她就只剩这么多了
After the fire, that's all that was left of her.
特丽雅 我真不知道
Talia. I can't decide
该说这是感人还是有病
if that's touching or morbid.
我猜真正的问题是
I guess the real question is,
你准备拿他们干嘛
what are you planning on doing with them?
我要问她一点事
I have to ask her something.
据我所知
And from what I've heard,
这是唯一可行的方法
this is the only way it's possible.
你特么在逗我
You gotta be kidding me.
你觉得我干嘛要把你的指头缝上
Why do you think I sewed your finger back on?
警长 警长
Sheriff? Sheriff.
嘿
Hey.
这些苍蝇来自巴罗的肿块
These dead flies everywhere They came out of Barrow. Out of his tumor.
怎么会这样
Is that even possible?
蛆会从身体里爬出来 这叫蛆虫病
Maggots can come from the body. It's called myiasis.
但是从胃里 这不太像
But from the stomach? It's not likely.
还有
And there's something else.
昨晚 他告诉我他为什么杀了那些小孩
Last night, he told me why he killed those teenagers.
我知道 我读了那篇报道 发光的眼睛
Yeah, I know. I read the report.Glowing eyes.
我们知道有这种年轻人
We know a few kids that fit that description.
听着 被偷的救护车找到了
Listen up, everyone. The stolen ambulance has been spotted.
在杜鲁门和斯波尔丁街角
Corner of Truman and Spaulding.
离学校只有三个街区
That's three blocks from the school.
快 我们走
Let's go. Go!
逗我吧
Oh, no.
绝对没可能
I don't think so.
你别以为在你杳无音讯两个周后突然出现
There's no way you come back here after two weeks of nothing,
带着你可爱的笑容 棕色的研眼睛
with your cute little smile, the dark eyes,
宽宽的额头 发达的肌肉
the brooding forehead, the muscles,
我就会再跟你在教练的办公室啪啪啪
and suddenly we're ripping each other's clothes off in Coach's office.
不可能 这不会发生的
No way. It's not gonna happen.
导员的办公室咋样
Guidance office?
去吧
Okay.
等等 等等 威廉姆斯·巴罗
Wait a minute, wait a minute! The William Barrow?
霰弹恐怖分子 就在这附近
The Shrapnel Bomber? Spotted nearby?
事实上比附近更近一些
A little closer than nearby, actually.
地下室怎么走
How do we get down to the basement?
我要知道每一个入口的位置
I need to know where every entrance is.
到时候没有人能够自由进出
I don't want anybody coming in or out of the school.
老爸 这里发生了什么
Dad, what's really going on here?
巴罗在找那些眼睛发光的人
Barrow went after kids with glowing eyes?
他的原话是什么
He said those exact words?
是的 没人知道他是怎么从麻醉状态里醒来的
Yeah. And no one knows how he woke up from anesthesia.
他们剖开他 发现了一个装满苍蝇的肿瘤
Just that when they opened him up, they found a tumor full of live flies,
那场面一定很了不起
which in any other circumstance would be all kinds of awesome.
你是说苍蝇
Did you say flies?
莉迪亚
Lydia?
我最近总是听到奇怪的声音
All day I have been hearing this sound.
就像
It's like...
嗡 嗡的
This buzzing.
像是苍蝇的声音吗
Like the sound of flies?
就是苍蝇的声音
Exactly like the sound of flies.
我不知道为啥你坐在这陪着我
All I'm saying is, I don't understand why you're sitting here with me
而不去餐厅找你的朋友玩
instead of in the cafeteria with the other kids.
要是我只是想陪陪你
Maybe I want to keep you company.
同学看到你和我一起 你该觉得不好意思 别陪我了
You should be embarrassed to be seen with me. Not keeping me company.
卡拉
Kira?
你必须去交朋友
You must have some friends by now.
我不知道我是咋回事 我在家有很多朋友的
I don't know what's wrong with me. I had a lot of friends back home.
但是在这 每次我一张嘴
But here it's like every time I open my mouth,
就像一个傻瓜一样 说话不着边际了
I just start rambling like an idiot.
屡败屡战 总好过
Try again. Fail again.
止步不前
Fail better.
那是萨缪尔·贝克特的话吗
Are you quoting Samuel Beckett to me?
我记得是犹大的话
I thought that was Yoda.
总会有人喜欢你的
Someone will show an interest.
你是一个漂亮的孩子
You're a beautiful girl.
谁会拒绝你
How could they not?
唯一一个喜欢我的是一个疯狂的狼
The only one who's shown any interest in me is a rabid coyote.
你也许可以与狼共舞
Maybe you could date the coyote?
我不需要约会 更不需要男朋友
I don't want a date. And I definitely don't need a boyfriend.
我只是想交朋友
I just want to make a few friends.
嘿哥们 你死哪去了
Hey, dude, where the hell have you been?
警察走了
The police are leaving.
他们为啥走
Why are they leaving?
警察吗
The police?
那意味着他们搜查完了 他不在这里
They must have cleared the building and grounds, which means he's not here.
-谁 你们到底在说...  -他一定在这里
- Who? What are you guys... - He has to be here.
那声音... 那苍蝇声
That sound... The buzzing I've been hearing?
越来越响了
It's getting louder.
有多响
How loud?
爸爸
Dad! Dad!
恩
Yeah?
你们不能走
You can't leave yet.
有目击者说他在火车站
We got an eyewitness that puts Barrow by the train station.
- 咱们走 斯特林斯基  - 等一下爸爸
- Let's go, Stilinski. - Whoa, whoa.Dad, please just...
莉迪亚说他还在这里
Lydia said that he's still here.
她看见了吗
Did she see him?
确切的说 没有
Not exactly. No.
但也不是完全没有 她有感觉的
Well, not at all actually. But she has a feeling.
超自然的感觉
A supernatural feeling.
莉迪亚不是棋子啊
Lydia wasn't on the chessboard.
现在是了
She is now.
- 变形怪 -不 是报丧女妖
- Kanima? - Um, Banshee.
- 哦 天哪 - 我知道这有多疯狂
- Oh, God. - I know. I know how it sounds.
大致上就是 他能感觉到有人快死了
But basically it means that she can sense when someone's close to death.
他感觉的到我要杀了你吗
Can she sense that I'm about to kill you?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧 看
All right, look,
我不是说我不相信你
I'm not saying I don't believe,
但是现在我更相信目击者
but right now, I'm going with eyewitness over Banshee.
我会留一些人的 学校封锁到三点
We're leaving a few deputies here. The school's on lockdown till 3:00.
没人出入
Nobody comes in, nobody goes out.
老兄 这是我现在能做的
Buddy, that's the best I've got right now.
我能最大能提供的 斯泰尔斯
That's the best I can give you, Stiles.
你把我留在这里 这不是...这是最糟糕的
You're leaving me here, that is not... That is the worst.
拿到了吗?
You got it?
答应我 小心点
Promise me you'll be careful.
我看到这个人的眼神了 很恐怖的
I looked right in this guy's eyes, and it was terrifying.
好 好的 妈 我保证
Yeah. Okay, Mom,I promise.
好吗 小心
Okay? Okay.
莉迪亚认为他还在这
Lydia thinks that he's still here even though
警察搜遍了全校
the cops searched the whole school.
但我们有一件他们没有
But they didn't have one thing...
那就是我们的嗅觉
Our sense of smell.
动物图鉴整整有一千多页
The Bestiary is literally 1,000 pages long.
如果我们要在这些文件里找到任何有关尸体
If I'm going to find anything about flies coming out of people's bodies,
这可要花上我整个晚上
it could take me all night.
记得吗
And remember, the word
苍蝇在古拉丁语是musca.
in archaic Latin for fly is musca.
知道了
Got it.
我们从哪里开始
Where do we start?
楼上
Upstairs.
我们必须走了
We gotta go.
所以现在怎么办
So this is how it's gonna be now?
我们信任他们吗
We trust them?
我让他们帮我们并不意味我相信他们
Just because I'm letting them help, doesn't mean I trust them.
嗯 好吧 我也不相信他们
Yeah, well, I don't trust them either.
或者有好感
Or like them.
实际上 我对他们恨之入骨
In fact, I hate them and just want them to die.
好吧 如果巴罗在这里并有自己的计划的话 你就放开做吧
Well, if Barrow's actually here and he's
got a plan, you might get what you want.
你发现什么了吗
You got something?
几个意思
Oh, really?
斯科特和艾塞克在地下室 是吗
Scott and Isaac are in the basement, right?
嗯 和伊桑和埃登在一起 计划是在中间
Yeah, with Ethan and Aiden. The plan is we meet in the middle,
锅炉房碰头
in the boiler room.
所有的狼人
All of the wolves...
眼睛会发光的
All of the ones with glowing eyes
都在地下室的锅炉房
are in the basement at the boiler room?
哦 天呐
Oh, my God!
一个王师傅可以用锅炉房炸掉整个学校的
An engineer could use a boiler room to blow up the whole school.
我们必须让他们离开那里
We have to get them out of there.
我们必须撤离所有人
We have to get everyone out.
我们该怎么做
How do we do that?
在恶作剧之夜拉响火灾警报就算了
Pulling a fire alarm on Mischief Night is one thing.
在谋杀现场旁边这么做你疯了吗!
Doing it when there's a mass murderer spotted nearby is insane!
如果是四年前的我 我揍死你了
If I was four years younger, I'd punch you.
怎么了 教练 这不科学
What? Coach, that doesn't make sense.
额 我觉得科学得很
Oh, well, it does to me!
这里
There.
我们什么也没找到
We didn't find anything.
甚至气味都没有
Not even a scent.
现在三点钟了 学校放学了
It's 3:00, so school's over.
如果这里有个炸弹 他会现在引爆吗
If there was a bomb, wouldn't he have set it off by now?
那是不是意味着大家安全了
Does that mean everybody's safe?
我不知道
I don't know.
我就...
I just...
我不知道
I don't know.
你声音放的多大?
How loud are you playing that thing?
走吧!快离开这里!
Let's go! Get the hell out of here!
你知道吗 这种仪式总会有点危险
You know, there's always an element of danger to rituals like this.
我实际上并不赞成这么做
I'm not particularly fond of them.
除非他们可以让我
Unless they somehow
从中受益
benefit me.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我想留着他们
I want to keep them.
情感价值
Sentimental value.
她是你妈妈 也是我的姐姐(妹妹)
She was your mother, but she was also my sister.
怎么 我就不能有一点情绪吗
What? Am I not allowed a little bit of sentiment?
- 太慢了 -不 不 等等
- Too long. - No! No, wait!
基拉
Kira?
准备吃饭吧 穿漂亮点
Get ready for dinner. And put on something nice.
我穿漂亮干嘛?
Why would I need to wear something nice?
我邀请了一个客人参加我称之为
I invited a guest for what I like to call the.
"险些让我女儿成为野狼晚餐的感恩餐"
"Thank You for Saving My Daughter from Becoming a Coyote Dinner" dinner.
你好
Hey.
哦 天辣
Oh, God.
斯科特 我确信作为一个本地的加州人
So, Scott, I'm sure that as a native Californian,
你肯定在日式寿司餐厅吃过
you've eaten at some pretty impressive Japanese sushi restaurants.
但是我可以告诉你我老公是很棒的主厨
But I have to tell you that my husband is a superb chef.
嗯 我们有惊起一油金鱼 海胆 鱼子和比目鱼
Okay, we have hamachi, uni, ikura, and hirame.
你以前没有吃过寿司吗 是吗
You've never eaten sushi before, have you?
他们都是生的吗
Is it all raw?
饭除外
Not the rice.
天啊 我们应该今晚吃意式千层面的
Oh, my God, guys. We were supposed to have lasagna tonight.
我只不过想让他留下个印象 我不想把这...
I was trying to impress him. I didn't want to bring out the...
那什么 我马上去做意式千层面
You know what? I'll make lasagna.
哦 不 不用了 我可以 我可以尝试任何东西 真的
Oh, no, no! It's okay. I can try anything. Really.
好吧
Okay.
这里 试着像握铅笔一样
Here. Try holding this one like a pencil.
这个指头放在下面 像这样 另一个放在上面
And this one goes under it, like this. Then you just move the top one,
- 像 像这样...  - 嗯 谢谢
- like, like this... - Yeah. Thanks.
寿司?
Sushi?
不同颜色的线是什么意思?
What do the different colored strings mean?
哦 代表不同的调查阶段
Oh, just different stages of the investigation.
绿色是解决了 黄色是待定 蓝色是快...
So green is solved, yellow is to
be determined, blue's just pretty...
- 红色是什么意思 - 没解决的
- What does red mean? - Unsolved.
墙上只有红色的
You only have red on the board.
是的 谢谢 我知道
Yes, I'm aware. Thank you.
你拉警报被扣留了么
Did you get detention for pulling the alarm?
是的 这星期每天都会 不要紧啦 我们在调查事情嘛
Yep. Every day this week. It's okay, though. We were onto something.
尽管我们没发现什么巴罗在那里的证据
Even though we couldn't find any proof of Barrow being there?
嘿 莉迪亚
Hey, Lydia.
每次发生什么的时候你总是对的 不是吗
You've been right every time something like this has happened, okay?
所以不要怀疑你自己了
So don't start doubting yourself now.
没有气味 没有炸弹
No scent. No bomb.
并且我麻烦你了
And I got you in trouble.
没事 听着 巴罗在那里 好吗
Okay, look. Barrow was there. All right?
你知道的 你感觉到了 不是吗
You knew it. You felt it. Okay?
听着 如果你想的话 我可以现在马上回学校查一晚上
And look, if you wanted to, I'd go back to
that school right now and search all night
来证实他
just to prove it.
起来 快起来 我们去学校
Get up. Get up now. We're going to the school.
带电的窗户
Electrified the windows?
是的
Yep.
不想说点什么吗?
Didn't wanna say anything about it?
-不想  -好吧
-Nope. -Okay.
你来这干嘛
What are you doing here?
我觉得你可以多一双眼睛
I figured you could use an extra pair of eyes.
你懂拉丁语
Can you read Latin?
不懂 但是我可以看图片
No. But I can look at pictures.
这肯定不是我的颜色
That's not exactly my color.
这极其疼的
This is going to be excruciatingly painful.
快做吧
Just do it.
我会的 我只是说一下
Oh, I'm going to. I just wanted you to know
我们都有一点小报复
we all have our petty revenges.
你们从纽约搬到这来的
So you guys moved here from New York?
我家几代都在这里
I have family ties here. Several generations.
幸村是日本人 是吗
Yukimura is Japanese, right?
嗯 是的
Mmm-hmm. Yes.
但是我实际上是韩国人 我和妻子结婚后
Yes, but I'm actually Korean. When my wife and I married,
我跟她姓 因为他是她们家唯一的幸存者
I took her name, as she was the only surviving member of her family.
你不想跟姓两个吗
You didn't want to take both names?
日本的婚姻法律规定
We were married in Japan, where the law says that the couple
我们只能有一个姓 姓koseki
must share the same name. To belong to the same koseki.
我妻子的血统很独特 实际上我准备在课堂上讨论它的
My wife's lineage is quite unique. I was actually going to discuss it in class.
不要啊
Please don't.
基拉 你应该对你的遗传感到自豪
Kira. You should be proud of your heritage.
能够融入你妈妈的家庭很荣幸
It was a profound honor to join your mother's family.
斯科特? 你的芥末怎么了
Scott? What happened to your wasabi?
我以为这是色拉酱
I thought it was guacamole.
所以我们在找啥
So what are we looking for?
那玩意儿好像是锁着的
That was supposed to be locked.
是啊我知道 还发现什么别的了么
Yeah. I know. Notice anything else?
闻起来像化学试剂
It smells like chemicals.
他们就不会追寻到他的气味了
They wouldn't have been able to catch his scent.
他曾在这儿给自己动了个小手术
He was here, performing very minor surgery on himself.
你说得对
You were right.
但是为什么我感觉不妙
Then why don't I feel good about this?
也许是因为他在这儿杀了人
Probably because he was here to kill somebody.
是谁 我们必须找出是谁
But who? That's what we gotta figure out.
我们分头行动 找找线索
We could spread out, start looking for... Anything.
莉迪亚 那些是什么
Lydia, what are those?
化学原子序数
Atomic numbers.
这是分子式吗
Is it a formula?
不是 19号元素是钾 53号元素是碘 88号元素是镭
Not really. 19's potassium. 53's iodine. 88's radium.
前两种元素生成了碘化钾
The first two make potassium iodide...
你确定是钾吗
Potassium is K?
源自于拉丁文Kalium 科学上管这叫拉丁语名
From kalium, the scientific neo-Latin name.
镭是什么
What's radium?
R-A.
基拉
Kira.
是啊 我刚吃了寿司 老妈
Yes, Mom. I ate sushi.
我都不知道你会使筷子了
I didn't even know that you could use chopsticks.
- 老妈 我想问你点事  -说吧
- Mom, can I ask you something? - Yeah.
你为什么不 你为什么不把姓换回成德尔加多
Why didn't you... How come you never changed your name back to Delgado?
我为什么保留了你父亲的姓吗
Do you mean, why did I keep your father's name?
- 是啊  - 好吧 因为那也是你的姓 亲爱的
- Yeah. - Yeah. Because it's your name, too, honey.
我得走了 宝贝儿 行么 我爱你
I gotta go, sweetheart, okay? I love you.
哦 感谢上帝 我可不是故意的
Oh, thank God. No offense to sushi.
呵呵 也许我们应该先招待你一些加州寿司卷才对
Yeah, we probably should have started you out on California rolls.
找到什么了么
You find anything?
有一份文献说苍蝇可以给死人传递信息
There's a reference about flies being able to carry messages to the dead.
你呢
What about you?
巴力西卜 苍蝇之王
Oh, just... Beelzebub, the Lord of the Flies.
你确定
Are you serious?
干嘛
What?
你是想吻我
You were just trying to kiss me.
不是的
No, I wasn't.
那你要干嘛 用头撞我么
Then what were you trying to do? Head-butt me?
好吧 也许我真的想吻你
All right, maybe I was trying to kiss you.
你脱线了吧
Are you completely, totally out of your mind?
你真的以为我会吻你吗
You actually think that I would want to kiss you?
或者 或者说再吻其他的狼人
Or... Or any other werewolf again?
相信我 我是绝对不会吻你的
Because trust me on this, I would never kiss you. Ever.
- 绝不  - 绝不 好吧 行
- Never. - Never. Okay. All right, fine.
我不也不会亲你
I won't kiss you either.
艾莉森 来我办公室
Allison. Can I see you in my office?
我把枪放哪儿了
Where I keep my guns.
又是和狼人
Another werewolf?
你看见她了吗 你问了什么
Did you see her? What did you ask her?
她有提到我吗
Did she say anything about me?
我操 情况不妙啊
Well, that doesn't look good.
- 谢谢你的晚餐  - 是谢寿司还是披萨
Thanks for dinner.For the sushi or the pizza?
呵呵 披萨不错
Uh... The pizza was good.
你看起来不错啊帅哥
You seem like a really nice guy.
不只因为是你救了我
And not just because you kept me from getting eaten by a coyote.
我还做了什么
Did I do something else?
你记得我的名字
Yeah. You remembered my name.
斯科特
Scott!
斯科特 快醒醒
Scott? Scott!
巴罗带走了科拉
Barrow, he took Kira!
我们知道 他一直跟着她
We know. He was after her the whole time.
什么都没有 只有有关苍蝇和死人的东西
No, nothing. Just stuff about flies and the dead. Nothing else.
好吧 谢谢
All right, thanks.
我们得想办法 他会杀了她的
We have to think of something. He's going to kill her.
我知道他在那 我咋知道的
I knew he was there. How did I know that?
因为你听见苍蝇了是吗
Because you heard the flies, right?
你现在听见了啥
What do you hear now?
什么都没 我觉得我能帮上忙
Nothing. I feel like I can do this.
但我不知道咋做
But I don't know what to do.
但是 就像是话都到嘴边了 我就是不知道该怎么说
It's like it's on the tip of my tongue,
and I don't know how to trigger it.
我只想尖叫... 我对天发誓 我是真的真的想大叫
I just... I swear to God, it literally makes me want to scream.
好吧 那就叫出来吧
Okay, then scream. Lydia, scream.
没苍蝇了
It's not flies.
是电流
It's electricity.
等下 巴罗是电力工程师
Wait a second, Barrow was an electrical engineer.
他在变电站工作
He worked at a power substation.
哪个变电站
What substation?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
现在 现在么
Right now? Ah. Right now,
我要给你照张相
I'm gonna take your picture.
只是证明我们在一起
Just a little proof of our time here together.
证明给那些不相信的人
A little proof for all of those people who never believed.
好吧 照了 可以让我走了么
Okay, you got your picture. You want to let me go now?
你看过 诅咒的村庄 这部电影吗
Did you ever see a movie called Village of the Damned?
原版的 不是再制版的 没人在意再制版的
The original. Not the remake. Nobody cares about crappy remakes.
我是说1960年的那部经典黑白片
I'm talking about the 1960 black-and-white masterpiece.
拍的是那些有着漂亮头发
It's about this group of children. Blonde-haired,
唯美的少年
beautiful children
他们的眼睛能发光
who can make their eyes glow.
他们做很坏很坏的事
And they do terrible, terrible things.
海报上写着他们的口号
The tag line on the poster read,
“当心他们麻痹了世人的的眼睛”
"Beware the stare that will paralyze the will of the world."
现在我告诉你们我看见了眼睛发光的孩子
Now, when I told everyone that I saw children with glowing eyes,
你们不相信我 我想让他们行动起来
they wouldn't believe me. I tried to get them to do something.
但他们不关心 不在意
But they wouldn't budge. They wouldn't move.
就像他们已经被麻痹了
As if they had been paralyzed.
我要把人们从麻痹中叫醒
I am going to shake them out of their paralysis.
我要让他们行动起来 我要
I'm going to get them moving. I'm going to...
我要电醒他们
I am going to galvanize them.
好吧 等着 等警察来
Okay. Wait here, all right? Just wait for the cops to come.
为啥要我等
Me? Wait, why?
我只拿了一个棒
I only got one bat.
斯科特 不要
Scott! No!
小心
Look out!
别 你要... 你要找的不是她
Don't... She's not... She's not the one you want.
别
No...
不要
Don't.
停下来 不要
Stop! No!
艾萨克 艾萨克
Isaac! Isaac!
艾萨克 快开门
- Isaac! - Isaac, come on, open the door!
- Isaac! - Isaac, open up!